plusmo.com 2008-07-23

# Plusmo Mobile Widget Gallery

Privacy Policy 

We take your privacy very seriously. Information you share with   
us is used for Plusmo's business purposes. Plusmo is not in   
the business of selling information about you. This notice tells   
you what information we collect, steps we take to protect and secure it, how we use and share the information, and finally, how you can contact us with questions or concerns. 

#### Information We Collect

#### Information voluntarily provided by you

  * Not all Plusmo services require you to provide personal information. You may use several areas of the site such as search, view content or browse the site without registering on the site. 
  * When you decide to subscribe to content from our site to your phone, we ask for your mobile phone number, your mobile operator and email address. This creates an account for you on our site. We need this information to deliver the service to your device. 
  * When you download the Plusmo software onto your mobile phone, it includes a unique identifying number so that we provide a personalized experience to your mobile phone. 

#### Automatic Data Collection

  * "Cookies" are small files web sites place on your hard drive that allow sites to identify you. The use of cookies is a common practice on many web sites. For example, if you allow a site to remember your login name or password, the site places a cookie on your computer. Cookies cannot read any other information on your hard drive. We may place cookies on your computer to allow us to identify you. We may use cookies to measure web site traffic, to offer you certain services, or to customize your visit. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 
  * An "IP address" is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP address probably varies from session to session. 
  * Plusmo automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, the date and time of your query, browser type, cookie information, and the page you request. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services. 
  * Plusmo also receives information about your mobile phone when you access the service from your mobile phone. This is non personal information that we use to help us identify your phone, and information about your phone such as screen dimensions, the kind of media formats supported by your phone, and memory available for use. We use this information to improve our service and support tailoring the service to the device (such as resizing pictures, restricting the amount of content based on your available memory). 

#### How we use the Information

We do not rent or sell your personally identifying information to third parties.

  * Mobile Phone Number and Mobile Operator: We use this to send an SMS/ Text message (Short Message Service) to the your phone, and to uniquely identify your account. 
  * Mobile Phone Type: We use this information to deliver the right version of software that is suited to your mobile phone. (such as a J2ME compatible version or Windows Mobile compatible version of the software). 
  * Email address: If your mobile phone supports emails, we may use this to send you a link to download the Software to your phone and to uniquely identify your account. We will send you administrative messages and email updates regarding your account. We may also send you notices of new content that has been added in which you may be interested, as part of the Plusmo service. In some cases, we may also send you primarily promotional messages. You may opt out of receiving any of these messages by canceling your User account. 

#### Security

Reify endeavors to protect the security of your personal information and your choices for its intended use. We store your account information on a secure server, and use procedures designed to protect the personal information we collect from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction. 

Although we will take (and require our third-party providers to take) commercially reasonable security precautions regarding your personal information collected from and stored on the Site, due to the open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that any of your personal information stored on our servers, or transmitted to or from a user, will be free from unauthorized access, and we disclaim any liability for any theft or loss of, unauthorized access or damage to, or interception of any data or communications. By using the Site, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks. 

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send any personal information to us by email. However, doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. We follow commercially reasonable security precautions to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during the transmission and once we receive it. 

#### Public Forums

Our web site offers developer forums and message boards. Please be advised that any information posted in these venues will be publicly available. 

#### Queries and Changes to Your Personal Information

If you have a question or comment about the Plusmo site or a request to correct or delete your personal information, please send it to us by using our web site Feedback form. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to fulfill your request in a timely manner. However, even if Plusmo deletes such personal information from its 'live' database(s), it may still be stored on other databases (including those kept for archival purposes). 

#### Linked Sites

Our site may link to other sites not controlled by Reify. We are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of any other web sites. We therefore encourage you to read the privacy policies on those other sites. 

#### Your Acceptance of this Privacy Policy

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. As we update and diversify our services, this Privacy Policy may evolve. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time so visitors are encouraged to review this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please check this page for updates periodically. We will also try to post any changes to this Privacy Policy before they become effective. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes. 

#### Contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the privacy practices of Reify, Inc, you can email us at [privacy-policy@plusmo.com.](mailto:privacy-policy@plusmo.com)
